<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cosmosporia</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cosmosporia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:51:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://example.com/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 21:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Cosmosporia - neologism derived from the Greek roots kosmos (divine order, universe) and spora (to spread, to sow). The establishment of a spacefaring civilization.
Cosmosporia is a work-in-progress game for PC made with the Godot engine. In it, the player is tasked with managing a space program whose purpose is to bring humanity into space, to the planets and eventually to the stars beyond. The focus is on designing space stations, surface bases, modular ships and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>-=About the Game=-</title>
      <link>https://example.com/game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 18:55:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/game/</guid>
      <description>🛰Build Modular Space Stations Stations are the heart of the game. Start with a core module and send up more to expand. Utility modules provide habitation, power and storage. Science modules enable researching new technologies to build better stations and improve logistics to reach further and further from the home world.
👩‍🚀👨‍🚀Recruit &amp;lsquo;Nauts &amp;lsquo;Nauts (both cosmo- and astro-) keep your stations up and running. Ensure they have enough supplies, and make sure to change them out frequently to keep them healthy and ready for the next expedition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://example.com/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 21:55:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/gallery/</guid>
      <description>This game is heavily work-in-progress, but here are some super early videos and assets. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the Creator</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 1970 20:23:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Silver Alicorn&amp;rdquo; is the pseudonymous creator of Cosmosporia. They currently resides somewhere in southern California. Their hobbies include hiking, pinball, reading and writing science fiction, writing music and hacking electronics. Their favorite authors include Iain M. Banks, Adrian Tschaikovsky, Ann Leckie, Yoon Ha Lee and Ursula K. Le Guin. Favorite video games are Kerbal Space Program, Juno: New Origins, Mass Effect, Elite Dangerous, Civilization: Beyond Earth&amp;hellip; you get the idea. Space.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
